Dwayne Moore

Customer Support Professional

Address Toronto, ON, M2N 7E3

Phone 416 875 9737

E-mail dwayne@dwaynemoore.me

Twitter https://twitter.com/DwayneEMoore
LinkedIn https://linkedin.com/in/dwaynemoore
WWW https://dwaynemoore.me

I am a dedicated, passionate, high-energy Customer Support Professional with 20+ years of experience in technology. I deliver highly effective solutions to customers' concerns by collaborating across all parts of an organization. I strive not only to be always learning and growing, but to help my co-workers to do the same, as it is the strength of a team that allows it to succeed.

Skills

Technical Support

Troubleshooting

Software Development

Operating Systems: macOS, Windows, UNIX/Linux, Android, iOS

Programming: C, C++, JavaScript, HTML, SQL, Shell Scripting, XML

Software: Slack, Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook), Google Suite (email,

sheets, slides, calendar)

Social Media: Later, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Reddit, Buffer, HootSuite

CRM Software: Zendesk, HubSpot

Work History

2021-05 - Current

Outbound Customer Service Representative

Invoice Simple, Remote

- Calling customers and informing them of change in payment processor
- Instructing customers on actions they need to take to prepare for the change
- Addressing questions and concerns about the change

2007-11 - 2015-02

Assistant Product Manager

IBM, Toronto, Ontario

- Supported sales and marketing organizations by answering clients' questions and concerns, creating marketing collateral, and presenting
- Managed social media presence
- Collaborated with development to address client requirements, questions, and concerns.

- Analyzed trends and performed causal revenue analysis
- Closed sales opportunities by assisting customers and sales teams

2005-06 - 2007-11

Enablement Focal Point

IBM, Toronto, Ontario

- Focused on clients' needs as well as needs of client-facing colleagues
- Educated development teams on clients' usage and issues with compilers, collaborating with them on resolutions.
- Provided feedback to development on design of new features.
- Increased quality by educating test teams on test coverage gaps

2001-02 - 2005-06

Customer Support Team Lead

IBM, Toronto, Ontario

- Assisted sales and marketing teams with compiler-related opportunities.
- Engaged clients to successfully use compiler products
- Decreased development team workload by increasing quality of bug reports
- Provided consistent customer experience and reduced escalations by holding problem-handling process reviews

Education

1990-09 - 1995-05

Bachelor of Science: Honors Computing And Computer Electronics

Wilfrid Laurier University - Waterloo, Ontario

Certifications

2020-04

Certified Customer Success Manager